<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.xronos.orcc.feature"
      label="Feature"
      version="2.1.2.qualifier"
      provider-name="EPFL">

   <description url="https://github.com/orcc/xronos/">
      Xronos: High Level Synthesis of Streaming Applications is a collection
of tools under GNU GPL3, Apache 2, and BSD licences created by EPFL, and
IETR/INSA (and Xilinx for OpenForge HLS) for the RVC-CAL dataflow
programming language.
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.example.com/copyright">
      Copyright (c) 2009-2014, EPFL
All rights reserved
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.example.com/license">
      XRONOS, High Level Synthesis of Streaming Applications
  
Copyright (C) 2014 EPFL SCI STI MM
 
XRONOS is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
(at your option) any later version.
 
XRONOS is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.
 
You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with XRONOS.  If not, see &lt;http://www.gnu.org/licenses/&gt;.
  
Additional permission under GNU GPL version 3 section 7
  
If you modify this Program, or any covered work, by linking or combining it
with Eclipse (or a modified version of Eclipse or an Eclipse plugin or 
an Eclipse library), containing parts covered by the terms of the 
Eclipse Public License (EPL), the licensors of this Program grant you 
additional permission to convey the resulting work.  Corresponding Source 
for a non-source form of such a combination shall include the source code 
for the parts of Eclipse libraries used as well as that of the  covered work.
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="Open RVC-CAL Compiler - Stable releases" url="http://orcc.sourceforge.net/eclipse"/>
   </url>

   <plugin
         id="org.xronos.orcc"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
